{
    "subject": "resource/Niantic,_Inc.",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "mobile applications, mobile games, alternate reality games",
    "human_readable": "Niantic Inc. is involved in the industry of mobile applications, mobile games, and alternate reality games.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9461024403572083,
            "question": "What industry is Niantic Inc. involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219158291816711,
            "question": "Are mobile games a major part of Niantic Inc.'s business?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8996250033378601,
            "question": "Does Niantic Inc. create mobile applications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701782822608948,
            "question": "What technologies are likely used in Niantic Inc.'s games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676214218139648,
            "question": "How has Niantic Inc. impacted the gaming industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7195777297019958,
            "question": "What types of games does Niantic Inc. develop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7074733972549438,
            "question": "Give examples of games developed by Niantic Inc."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548073887825012,
            "question": "What makes Niantic Inc.'s games unique compared to traditional games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6228263974189758,
            "question": "What is the target audience for Niantic Inc.'s games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6037159562110901,
            "question": "What is an alternate reality game?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Niantic Inc. is involved in the industry of mobile applications, mobile games, and alternate reality games.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2554_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the target audience for Niantic Inc.'s games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2554_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Niantic Inc.'s games unique compared to traditional games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2554_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give examples of games developed by Niantic Inc.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2554_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2554_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about Niantic Inc., its business model, and its involvement in developing augmented reality (AR) games such as Pok\u00e9mon GO, Ingress Prime, and others. The company is described as operating in the global gaming and technology market, focusing on both casual and dedicated gamers who enjoy interactive and immersive experiences. It also mentions that Niantic offers mobile games which include NBA All Worlds, Pikmin Bloom, pokemon GO and Ingress Prime. This supports the triple statement about Niantic Inc. being involved in the industry of mobile applications, mobile games, and alternate reality games."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Niantic Inc.'s involvement in mobile applications (specifically mobile games) and augmented reality (AR), which falls under the broader category of alternate reality games. Therefore, the statement \"Niantic Inc. is involved in the industry of mobile applications, mobile games, and alternate reality games\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}